In Chapter 14 of Nekros,
the crime scene is…
A warehouse by the pier.
Are you saying Kaye is Mr. Kill, Praew?
You’re the only person who knows
what’s going on in the murderer’s head.
Work with me.
The victim in Chapter 18 of Nekros
is a dirty politician.
The MP is recently
taking a meditation retreat
at a temple in the suburbs.
Can I ask you something?
Why did you write Nekros?
My family was ruined
because of the Thai Investment Bank case.
I’ll prove to you
that this world
doesn’t need a monster like Nekros.
Someone’s trying to break in.
Get ready to seize him!
Let go!
Who the hell are you?
I said let go of me!
Why are you restraining me?
It’s not what you think, officer.
I’m just…
I’m a reporter.
Reporter?
What are you doing here?
I…
(Sir, multiple cars
are approaching the temple’s gate.)
Try and take as much footage as possible.
You two, just take some photos
with the small cameras.
No need to come in.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Come on.
Stay calm.
I’m a police officer.
Please stay calm.
MP Jaratphong is here, isn’t he?
We just need an interview.
No, you can’t. Please stay calm.
Excuse me.
Mr. MP is unavailable
for an interview right now.
Thank you.
Unavailable?
It will only take a minute!
So the video with those women is real?
Phat?
What do you think
you’re doing to my friend?
Oh, no. This is my brother.
It’s nothing.
Phat.
Are you here because of
that leaked video, too?
What video?
What are reporters doing here?
We’re here to ask the MP
about the leaked video.
The temple sex tape.
You don’t know that?
Video? What video?
Why don’t I show you?
It’s been trending.
TWO-FACED MP HAVING AN ORGY IN A TEMPLE.
RELIGIOUS MAN, MY FOOT.
If you’re not here because of this,
what are you here for?
-Please stay calm.
-Is that sex tape real?
Please stay calm.
Why is the police getting involved?
Don’t tell me the MP is hiring cops
as his private guards.
That’s not the case.
I’m just here to do my job.
What sort of things are you here to do?
Can you tell us that?
Tell us.
Just tell us.
I’m the leader of this team.
I apologize but we cannot give you
any details right now.
Police Major Yotsaphat Traikanawut.
I believe I smell something fishy.
Mr. Thun Thawikorn Putthanan.
Isn’t it?
You’re an amazing reporter.
You’re quite famous, too.
You must know a thing or two
about press ethics
and the right of privacy.
I think you’re investigating
the serial murder case
concerning the manga Nekros.
It’s plain as day that the murderer
is still out there.
I don’t think you have enough time
on your hand
to be serving a random politician,
not unless you think MP Jaratphong
could be Nekros’ next victim.
Is that the case?
It’s a goddamn small room!
Keep freaking looking!
Huh?
Did you find it?
Or are you waiting for me
to get thrown in jail first?
Damn it, it’s a tiny room!
We found the cameras, sir.
Shit!
There must be a mole.
Find him!
And when I find out who did this,
I’ll make sure his family
goes through hell!
Get it done as soon as possible.
You should leave, sir.
I’ll handle the rest.
Damn it!
Sir!
Where are you going? What about us?
Inspector, is that true?
Is MP Jaratphong the next victim?
-Is that true?
-Is it true?
Well, Inspector?
Why not take this opportunity
to give us an update on the investigation?
We’re all here, after all.
He’s right, sir. You should.
The investigation is confidential right now.
Once the time is right,
we’ll definitely hold a press conference.
Alright.
I’m just worried about the MP, is all.
Seeing Nekros’ previous victims…
It wouldn’t be a surprise
if the next victim was MP Jaratphong.
Let’s hope that’s not the case.
MP Jaratphong is leaving!
Look!
She’s right.
Mr. MP!
Sir!
We just need an interview.
We just have a few questions.
Sir! Sir!
-Why are you doing this?
-Sir!
We have a few questions!
-Give us an interview!
Sir! Answer the questions!
Wait!
That’s not the MP!
Who’s that?
Where’s the real MP?
What the hell are those cops doing here?
And when this gets to my party,
I’m gonna be in trouble.
I can’t be losing my MP chair.
Why the hell did you stop?
Hurry up and take me to the car!
You want all those reporters to get here?
Wait, wait, wait!
Are you sure it was MP Jaratphong?
It was quite dark, but…
I’m sure it was him.
Radio all police stations.
Tell them this is urgent.
Set up checkpoints scanning
every opaque white van
within the 10-20 kilometer radius
from here.
Every single van.
-Yes, sir.
Good work today, everyone.
See you at the office tomorrow.
Inspector, the press is already writing
about MP Jaratphong.
They work fast.
Praew, go home.
What?
You’re hurting me.
Let go.
Did you sneak into my room
to get information just
so Tun could have some headlines?
Do you realize what he did?
Reporters are making things harder.
That kind of news is
a window of opportunity for the murderer.
If that MP actually ended up dead,
how would you reporters
take responsibility for this?
You’re just an intern.
You’re not even a real reporter.
And stop letting that jerk
mess with your head!
He’s just using you to get some scoop.
No one’s messing with my head!
I’m just being myself.
And that MP is a bad guy.
I might be an intern,
but I’m just doing what I think is right.
I don’t want to be ignorant like some cops
or a dirty cop like Dad.
Lies become truths
if the person who knows the truth
chooses to stay silent.
I won’t let that happen.
Thank you for choosing
to do the right thing.
Get in the car. I’ll give you a ride.
It’s okay.
I can go home by myself.
You should talk to your sister.
Nah.
I’ll give you a ride.
Praew won’t listen to me anyway
whatever I say right now.
Thank you.
You can let me off here, Inspector.
I know a shortcut.
Sure.
Thank you.
Eat lots.
And you gotta do something
other than sleeping.
Why not just adopt them?
It’s better this way.
If one day I’m gone,
someone will take care of them.
Ever since I lost my family,
I’ve been on my own.
No one is ever there to knock some sense
into me when I do something wrong.
That’s why I think
even though your sister is being stubborn
or saying something mean to you,
maybe she’s just trying to prove herself
to you as her brother.
Don’t be mad at her.
And don’t blame yourself.
I think, as a big brother,
you’re already doing your best.
You sure are talkative today.
You usually aren’t.
But… Thank you.
Bye.
Well, I’d better go.
Goodnight, Inspector.
(I don’t want to be ignorant
like some cops)
or a dirty cop like Dad.
Inspector.
This is the report of
the interrogation of everyone
on the night the MP disappeared.
The head of security said
one of the guards
took the MP out the back door.
I asked him to show me who that guard was.
But as it turned out, that man
faked his identity to secure this job.
I’m already looking into that.
And the van?
No report from any checkpoints
about any suspicious vans.
If that man really was Nekros,
by the time we learned who he is,
the MP would become a lifeless body.
You have something to say?
Go for it.
I’m not sure if this is useful,
and I don’t know
if I remember everything correctly.
What are you talking about?
Can I have some paper?
That’s an old model,
but a popular one.
It’s still too common.
I remember something else.
Here.
I remember the dent in the car
and the tattoo of the person
who likely took MP Jaratphong.
That narrows it down.
Get our intel team to look into
any criminal records that went to court.
Even rumors or accusations.
Check all the places
with a history of crimes
with the MP’s name involved.
If you ever run into the man
who took the MP,
by all means assume that
he is our killer, Nekros.
-Yes, sir.
Thanks for this.
I want you to try and remember…
the last page of that manga.
If you did,
it would be a big help to us.
I believe in you.
Of course.
Can you show me that one?
(From the video leaked on social media
regarding MP Jaratphong,)
(which reporters were on location
to investigate two nights ago,)
(including us at Thun Insight,)
(it seems things have escalated.)
That’s the guy.
(MP Jaratphong disappeared
right in front of our eyes)
(and Inspector
Yotsaphat Trikanawut’s team.)
(Seeing as his team
is responsible for investigating…)
(kidnappings and serial killers,)
(it is quite notable that
there are three cases involving)
(some form of corruption.)
Thanks.
(…a connection between these cases
and the manga, Nekros.)
Hmm.
Thanks.
(I don’t think it was a coincidence)
(that the police officer responsible
for the case and his team)
(was at the scene.)
(I don’t think it is right
to assume, however.)
(Whether MP Jaratphong is a good
or bad person, no one can confirm.)
(as long as we do not have any proof,
the MP is an innocent man.)
Can you find out
where this tattoo parlor is?
It’s a mess online.
I can’t tell what is true
and what is not anymore.
Who’s to say it’s not all true,
Lieutenant?
I know dude’s a jerk.
I just didn’t expect him
to be down right evil.
Any updates?
There are two, sir.
We found the van.
After cross-referencing
from Kaye’s sketch,
here it is.
And one more thing,
from the sketch of the tattoo,
when cross-referencing
with criminal records and medical history,
we got our guy.
Thank you.
His name is Kim.
I’m looking for him.
Good job.
Excuse me, sir.
Can I see that?
You’re observant.
And you’re very detail-oriented.
No wonder you’re a popular manga artist.
I’m not that observant
if I don’t remember everything.
What I wrote, that is.
It’s okay.
If we put all our effort together
and actually catch Kim,
we won’t need the manga anymore.
Right.
PROTECTING BAD GUYS
WITH TAXPAYER MONEY IS INSANE.
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT THE POLICE TO DO?
LET PEOPLE DIE?
I BET THE POLICE WON’T LIFT A FINGER
IF THE VICTIMS AREN’T HIGH-PROFILE.
HOW MANY BODIES DID HE CLAIM? IT’S SCARY.
I HOPE HE GETS CAUGHT SOON.
ALL THE VICTIMS WERE CORRUPTING JERKS
WHO DESERVED IT.
THERE’S TOO MUCH CORRUPTION
AND WE NEED SOMEONE TO REORGANIZE IT.
Seems like the manga really won over.
It’s just a trend, you know.
I just… feel like
I’m doing something wrong
when all I’ve been doing
is enforcing the law.
It’s been three days now, too.
And the situation hasn't improved.
I bet I’m looking for a body
this time as well.
Your sister is better at this
than you are, huh?
Look at Praew.
No matter what mean things
you threw at her,
she didn’t falter.
She didn’t give up on her duty.
So, you shouldn’t give up either.
You know who you’re doing all this for.
DO YOUR BEST, BRO.
PREAW SENT A STICKER.
I’m lucky, aren’t I?
I have a great sister.
And I have a great partner.
Inspector.
We found where Kim’s laying low.
We have eyes on it right now.
Inspector.
Our informant said Kim’s hideout
is on this street.
This is the van.
It’s the same van I saw the other night.
Whoa…
What a sicko.
You okay?
Yeah.
MEMORIALS OF EVIL
Does he have a notebook like this
for the other victims, too, I wonder…
I don’t know anymore
whether the victims or the murderer
that’s more of a sicko.
Why don’t you wait outside?
Let me handle it here.
This is all the evidence we need.
Issue an arrest warrant.
-Yes, sir.
WANTED
ANAN PRATONNGAM, AGE: 26 FOR MURDER
MEMORIALS OF EVIL
Please…
Please, let me go.
Why are you doing this to me?
I’ve never done anything to you.
Please.
Please…
I’ve never done anything to you.
No!
It’s been three days.
Are we to go back to
looking for a body again?
It’s only been a few hours
since we released that wanted poster,
and everyone online is already
lauding him as a hero.
People are rooting for him
to kill MP Jaratphong before we catch him.
What’s wrong with the world?
How come we’re the bad guys here?
Just focus on working
instead of complaining, Nop.
Give me MP Jaratphong’s info.
Yes, sir.
Here it is.
For everything he did,
one death wouldn’t be enough
to pay for it.
We all know he is responsible
for all his crimes.
Are we really working our butts off
to save the worst guy ever?
Listen.
I want you all to go back to
the most basic question:
What is a police officer’s duty?
Excuse me.
Can you show me the crime scenes
of all three cases again?
An abandoned warehouse,
a field,
and a warehouse by the river.
Those are the three locations
the murderer chose.
Memorials of Evil.
What’s that?
Oh, right.
The notebook at Kim’s place
jogged my memory.
Memorials of Evil is a name used to mark
the locations where the bodies are found
in the Nekros manga.
These places are well thought out
and make sense for each victim.
Uh, yes, I did come up with it,
but I think the murderer
used the same logic
to deal with the bodies.
Do you have all three victims’ profiles?
Of course.
What do you think, Inspector?
We’re on the same page, aren’t we?
I believe we are.
Can you please explain how you understand
the idea of Memorials of Evil?
From my understanding,
each crime scene has
something to do with the cases
the victims were involved in.
And according to the manga Nekros,
those places would be called
Memorials of Evil
In other words,
these are the places the victims
once used for their own gain.
Am I correct?
Exactly.
For example, the first case
is the businessman.
The body was found
at an abandoned warehouse.
He was the businessman behind
a swindling case with over 40,000 victims,
where he refused to pay
for his employees’ compensation.
And that factory…
is now the abandoned warehouse
which is the crime scene.
Am I right?
The second victim was
a former Permanent Secretary.
And his body was found in a field.
Oh, I remember this case
because I was investigating it.
The field where the body was found
was expropriated
when the victim was in office.
It was huge on the news.
There was a scramble on the land,
and next thing we knew,
the land was passed on to some investors.
What about the third case?
Attorney Komkrit.
What do you think, Inspector?
What’s the connection here?
This warehouse by the pier
was once where the biggest stash of drugs
in our country’s history was hidden.
It belonged to one of Komkrit’s clients.
Of course the charges were dropped.
The fourth case…
MP Jaratphong.
I think MP Jaratphong is like
a corpse amped up on formalin
and dressed up to look presentable.
From the outside,
he’s shining and glorious,
but inside, he’s rotten.
That’s why I think
the crime scene Nekros means
for MP Jaratphong must be…
The temple he built.
Inspector.
Thank you for believing me.
I told you I believe you.
Why?
No reason.
I knew we’d find a body.
Secure all exits.
The murderer is still inside the temple.
Damn it.
It’s the same damn trick.
What a scum.
Hey!
Hey! Stop!
Kaye!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Phat?
Phat. Phat. Phat.
Phat!
Ph…
Shit!
Phat. Phat. Phat.
Phat.
Phat. Phat.
Phat. Phat. Phat.
Phat!
Shit!
Shit…
Phat. Phat.
Phat!
Show me your wound.
Why did you run after him?
What if he has a gun?
What if he shoots at you?
What will you do?
Well…
I saw he was running.
When it comes to hunting
the murderer down,
let me handle it.
Your job
is to stay alive until all this is over.
Got it?
See you at the car.
I’ll give you a ride home.
Thank you
for risking your life to save me.
Worried about me?
You’re thinking
his life’s miserable, aren’t you?
Do you really believe Kim is Nekros?
Cops can’t decide based on feelings.
Do you think Mr. Kill is proud of me?
If Kim wasn’t in custody right now,
who would be the next victim?
There are still so many things
Kaye doesn't know about.
For example… Your father’s case.